news10now.com 2018-06-24

# Privacy Policy | Syracuse Central New York | Spectrum News

The information TWC’s parent, Charter Communications, Inc. ("Spectrum") collects about you at this site and its sub domains (the "Site") is used to administer the Site and to provide information to visitors about the Site's various services and tools, and to provide general news, information and entertainment. Spectrum, together with Road Runner and Spectrum-affiliated cable operators, are collectively referred to in this Privacy Policy as "we," "us," "our" or other similar pronouns, or "Spectrum."

**What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**

This Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") applies to your use of the Site. This Privacy Policy does not govern Spectrum's treatment of information it collects and receives about you other than through the Site, for example in connection with any other services provided to you by Spectrum. A privacy notice relating to some of the other services Spectrum provides is located at help.twcable.com/html/policies.html

This Privacy Policy covers how Spectrum treats information that Spectrum collects and receives about you via the Site, including the personally identifiable information we collect through the various features, services, and software that we use to provide the Site to you. Some of these offerings are provided by third parties who may provide you with additional information and choices about your privacy. If you choose to take advantage of these offerings, you should read the privacy policies of such third parties.

**How Does Spectrum Collect and Use Information About You?**

Absent your consent or request, Spectrum does not divulge personally identifiable information to third parties for their marketing or advertising purposes.

When you visit the Site, it is important that we can present our content in a way that makes sense to your screen, that we are able to conduct research, that we know which pages and activity on the Site are most popular and, in some cases, that compensation can be determined between us and our content and advertising partners. In order to do these types of things, we may collect data such as:

  * The type of browser you use (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer, etc.);
  * The type of operating system you use (e.g., Apple Mac OS X, Windows XP, mobile Android or Apple OS, etc.);
  * The domain name of your Internet Service Provider (e.g., Road Runner);
  * Your Internet Protocol address;
  * The referring page that linked you to us, the pages you visit on this Site; the web page you visit after this Site;
  * The content and advertisements that you view and/or click on;
  * Any search terms you enter on this Site or a referral site;
  * If you are accessing this Site from a portable device, the device may provide this Site with your location, we will collect that information on pages where your location helps authenticate you or determine the page content. To the extent this information is stored; it will be stored only in anonymous or aggregate format.
  * In delivering a video service on the Site, we may also track information about your use of the Site in a non-personally identifiable manner and we may combine this information with other non-personally identifiable information. None of this data will be used to personally identify you.

Use of this Site is allowed only for people that are authenticated as Spectrum subscribers. In order to identify whether you are eligible to enter the Site and access particular content, we will collect information to authenticate you and the Spectrum services you purchase.

From time-to-time, this Site may offer features that will require us to collect information about you in order for the features to work in an optimum way. These features can include the registration or subscription to newsletters, accounts or features on this Site, the making of online purchases, entering sweepstakes and contests, completing surveys, contributing to a chat room, message board, blog, or other similar open forum on this Site, the submission of comments or question to us using a "contact us" or similar feature on this Site, the sending to Spectrum of e-mail, or in any other way submitting personally identifiable information to us via or relating to this Site. If you do not take advantage of these opportunities, we will not collect information from you to support these options.

To the extent you provide us with information about you, we may use this information for internal purposes related to any Spectrum service or product and to send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you.

Spectrum sites (other than this Site), as well as any other third party content, sites, advertisements, applications and toolbars linked to from this Site, may each have their own privacy policies and practices. Spectrum is not responsible for the information practices of third parties. You should carefully review their privacy policies in order to determine how each third party may use any personally identifiable information you provide.

Some of the information described above is collected or maintained through "cookies," which are small data files that are sent to your browser or related software from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Most Web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. Additionally, if you have a Flash player installed on your computer, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies (technically known as Flash "local shared objects"). However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Site or certain areas or features.

Many of the third party advertisers that place tracking tools on our Websites are members of programs that offer you additional choices regarding the collection and use of your information.  You can learn more about the options available to limit these third parties’ collection and use of your information by visiting the websites for the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.youradchoices.com/aboutus.aspx), as well as the webpages for [Facebook’s ad preferences tool](https://www.facebook.com/about/ads/) and [privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

Content on this Site, including advertisements, may be recommended to you or customized to your interests and preferences, based on your personally identifiable information and web site usage information, including (but not limited to) non-personally identifying information, which we may obtain from you or from other sources.

We may make available a service through which you can receive messages on your wireless device via short message service ("SMS Service"). You must first register and provide all required information, which may include, for example, your name, SMS address, wireless carrier and, if fees are applicable to the SMS Service you subscribe to, billing information (either your credit card information or mobile service carrier information if applicable fees will be billed through your carrier). We may also obtain the date, time and content of your messages in the course of your use of the SMS Service. We will use the information we obtain in connection with our SMS Service in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If fees are charged to your wireless account invoice, we may provide your carrier with your applicable information in connection therewith. Your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data about your wireless device usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies.

Any or all of the activities and collection described above may be performed on our behalf by our services providers.

**Does Spectrum Ever Share Information with Other Parties?**

Spectrum will not disclose information about you to any other party except under circumstances like the ones described below, or as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy or required or permitted by law:

  * If you express a desire for us to do so, we may share your personally identifiable information with third parties (such as co-sponsors of our sweepstakes, contests and other offerings) pursuant to the service that you desire.
  * Spectrum may share your information with its affiliates, service providers and other third parties that help to operate our business and this Site and deliver the products and services available on or through the Site.
  * When you contribute to a "public" area or feature of this Site, such as a chat room, bulletin board, blog or other open forum that we may make available on or through this Site, the information that you submit will be made available to other users. For this reason, we recommend that you not submit any sensitive information on these areas of the Site, including your full name, home address, phone number, financial information, or other information that would enable users to locate you.
  * Spectrum provides your information to trusted vendors who work on behalf of or with Spectrum and under confidentiality agreements. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * When Spectrum believes it should, it will respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, and to establish or exercise Spectrum's legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * Spectrum shares information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to Spectrum's property or the physical safety of any person, violations of Spectrum's terms of use or as otherwise allowed by law.
  * In the event that Spectrum, or any affiliated entity, or substantially all of its assets related to a particular geographical region, are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, user information may be one of the transferred assets.

Aggregate data and information that otherwise is not personally identifiable to you may be disclosed to others.

**Security**

Spectrum will take steps to protect the security and integrity of all sensitive information provided to this Site. However, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.

You are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you shall be responsible for any access to or use of the Site by you or any person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may change this Policy by amending the on-line version. If you continue to use this Site following any change in our Policy, you will have accepted the changes. If you do not agree to the changes, you should not use this Site. Any changes to this Notice are intended to be prospective only.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or the privacy practices of Spectrum in connection with this Site, you may contact us at [Privacy@Charter.com](mailto:Privacy@Charter.com).
